webanalyticsassociation.org 2015-12-07

# Digital Analytics Association

**Copyright**

Digital Analytics Association (“DAA”) maintains its website as a service to the Internet community. Access to and use of digitalanalyticsassociation.org is subject to the terms and conditions set forth herein and all applicable laws. DAA may revise these terms and conditions from time to time by updating this posting.

This site and all of its contents including, but not limited to, all text and images (“content”) are owned and copyrighted by DAA or others with all rights reserved unless otherwise noted. The content, without the express written permission of DAA or the rightful owner, may not be distributed, downloaded, modified, edited, reused, reproduced, transmitted, performed, displayed or otherwise used by any mechanical or electronic means, except as provided herein. 

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to the Digital Analytics Inc. (“DAA”) and its online community.  Our goal is to provide you with a personalized online experience that provides you with the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. This Privacy Policy has been written to describe the conditions under which the DAA website (the “site”) and the services available on the site are being made available to you by DAA. The Privacy Policy discusses, among other things, how data obtained during your visit to this Site may be collected and used. The Privacy Policy also discusses important limitations about the way you may use materials and services you find on the site.  Read the Privacy Policy carefully. By using this site, you will be deemed to have accepted the terms of this Policy.  If you do not agree to accept the terms of the Privacy Policy, you are directed to discontinue accessing or otherwise using the site or any materials obtained from it.

  We protect your personal information using industry-standard safeguards. We may share your information with your consent or as required by law as detailed in this policy, and we will let you know when we make significant changes to this Privacy Policy by posting changes to the site.

**IMPORTANT INFORMATION REGARDING YOUR ACCOUNT**

  **Sites Covered by this Privacy Policy   **

  This Privacy Policy applies to the DAA website (the “site” or the “sites”) located at http://www.digitalanalyticsassociation.org/privacypolicy.

  **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

  The process of maintaining a website is an evolving one, and DAA may decide at some point in the future, without advance notice, to modify the Privacy Policy by posting a new Policy on the site. Please review the changes carefully.  If you agree to the terms, simply continue to use the site.  If you object to any of the changes to the Privacy Policy, please do not continue to access the site, as your continued use of the site after we’ve posted a notice of changes to the Privacy Policy shall constitute your consent to the changed terms or practices. 

  **Children’s Privacy**

  DAA is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children, and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. DAA does not intentionally collect information from children under the age of 13, and DAA does not target its sites to children.  Only persons who are more than 18 years old or an emancipated minor may use the sites.  By accessing the sites, you are legally acknowledging that you are over the age of 18 or an emancipated minor.  If you are under the age of 18, you don’t have the legal right to access the sites.

  **California Shine the Light Law**

  California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us, once per calendar year, information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year. To obtain this information from us, please contact us, and choose "Request for California Privacy Information" for the subject of your message, and we will send you a reply e-mail containing the requested information. Not all information sharing is covered by the "Shine the Light" requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

  **Security**

  We have implemented industry-standard security safeguards designed to protect the personal information that you may provide.  We also periodically monitor our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks, consistent with industry standards.  You should be aware, however, that since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you submit to the site. There’s also no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.  It’s your responsibility to protect the security and integrity of your account details, including your username and password.  Please note that emails, instant messaging, and similar means of communication with other site users are not protected or encrypted, so you should not communicate any confidential information through these means.

**Registration**

  In order to use the DAA website, you may need to create an account by providing use with at least your name, email address, and a password. You can choose to provide other information about yourself during the registration process (for example, your gender, location, company affiliation, etc.). We use this additional information to provide you with more customized services, and this information may be viewable by others.  You understand that, by creating an account, DAA and others will be able to identify you by your profile, and you agree to allow DAA to use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use **[INSERT LINK TO TERMS OF USE]**. **You must follow this link to our Terms of Use in order to understand the terms of your relationship with (DAA).**

  On some pages of the site, you may be able to request information, subscribe to mailing lists, participate in online discussions, collaborate on documents, provide feedback, submit information into registries, register for events, apply for membership, or join technical committees or working groups. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, user IDs, passwords, billing information, or credit card information.  
**Account Profile Information   **

  Once you’ve created an account, you may choose to provide additional information on your user profile, such as descriptions of your job title, professional experience, your educational background, professional affiliations and memberships, and technical skills.  This information that you voluntarily provide may be seen by other users.

  **Non-Personal Information**

  Non-personal information is data about usage and service operation that is not directly associated with a specific personal identity.  DAA may collect and analyze non-personal information to evaluate how visitors use the site. 

  **Aggregate Information**

  DAA may gather aggregate information, which refers to information your computer automatically provides to us and that cannot be tied back to you as a specific individual. Examples include referral data (the sites you visited just before and just after our site), the pages viewed, time spent at our site, and Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.  An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet.  For example, when you request a page from one of our sites, our servers log your IP address to create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns and for purposes of system administration. 

  **Log Files and IP Addresses**

  We may collect information from the devices and networks that you use to visit the site in order to help improve the services we provide.  Every time you request or download a file from the site, DAA may store data about these events and your IP address in a log file.  We may use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use or for other business purposes.  When you access or leave the site by clicking on a hyperlink, we receive the URL from the site from which you last visited or the one to which you’re directed.  We may receive the Internet Protocol (“IP”) address of your computer or proxy server used to access the site, your operating system, the type of browser you used, and the type of device and/or operating system you use, your mobile device carrier or your ISP.  We also may receive location data passed to us from third-party services or GPS-enabled devices that you have set up in order to customize your experience based on location information.

  **Cookies**

  We use cookies and similar technologies, including mobile device identifiers, to help us recognize you when you log into our site.  By accessing the site, you are consenting to the placement of cookies and other similar technologies in your browser in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. 

  Cookies are small packets of information that a site’s computer stores on your computer. DAA can then read the cookies whenever you visit our site.  We may use cookies in a number of ways, such as to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, to deliver content specific to your interests and to track the pages you’ve visited.  These cookies allow us to use the information we collect to customize your experience so that your visit to our site is as relevant and as valuable to you as possible.  You may modify and control how and when cookies are set through your browser settings.  Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to control or reject cookies in the “Help” section of the toolbar.  We do not link non-personal information from cookies to personally identifiable information without your permission.

        FIRST PARTY COOKIES  
These are cookies that are set by this website directly.  Google Analytics:  We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behavior on this website.  Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on.  This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information.  We therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are.  
You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy regarding its Analytics service at: <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html>

  THIRD PARTY COOKIES AND PRIVACY POLICIES  
These cookies are set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site.  Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons across the site that allow visitors to share content on social networks such as LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook and Google+.  This site also uses the AddThis service.

  In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside our website.  You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on this website.

  The DAA website is hosted by Timberlake.com. You can view their privacy policy.

  SHOPPING CART  
We use a session cookie to remember your log-in for you and to remember what you’ve put in the shopping basket.  We consider these necessary to provide that service for you.  If these are disabled then it will disable other functionality on the site.

  PIXEL TAGS  
Like many websites, we may also use pixel tags, also known as beacons, spotlight tags or web bugs, to improve our understanding of site traffic, visitor behavior, and response to promotional campaigns, as a supplement to our server logs and other methods of traffic and response measurement. Pixel tags are sometimes used in conjunction with small Javascript-based applications, also for the purpose of traffic measurement. We may also implement pixel tags provided by other companies, for the same purpose. You can disable pixel tags by changing your browser settings to omit images and disable Javascript; or there are commercial software packages available that can omit pixel tags and most advertisements.

  CLICKSTREAM  
No clickstream data collection is being used for this website at the current time. However, we have many vendors who are the industry leaders in this area as members in the DAA.

        **New Technologies**

  As new technologies emerge, DAA may be able to improve our services or provide you with new ones, which means that DAA may create new ways to collect information on the site.  If we offer a new service or new features to our existing site, for example, these changes may result in our collecting new information in order to improve your user experience.

  **Personal Information**  
Personal information is information that is associated with your name or personal identity.  DAA uses personal information to better understand your needs and interests and to provide you with better service.  On some of our web pages, you may be able to request information, subscribe to mailing lists, participate in online discussions, collaborate on documents, provide feedback, submit information into registries, register for events, apply for membership, or join technical committees or working groups. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, user IDs, passwords, billing information, or credit card information.  
**Members-Only Web Site   **  
DAA may provide a members-only section of our web site.  Information you provide on DAA’S  membership application may be used to create a member profile, and some information may be shared with other of our individual member representatives and organizations.  Member contact information may be provided to other members on a secure web site to encourage and facilitate collaboration, research, and the free exchange of information among our members, but we expressly prohibit members from using member contact information to send unsolicited commercial correspondence.  DAA’S members automatically are added to our member mailing lists.  From time to time, member information may be shared with event organizers and/or other organizations that provide additional benefits to our members.  By providing us with your personal information on the membership application, you expressly consent to our storing, processing, and distributing your information for these purposes.  
**Company Information**  
Company information is information that is associated with the name and address of member organizations and may include data about usage and service operation. The primary representative of any our member organizations may request usage reports to gauge the extent of their employees’ involvement in consortium activities.  You should be aware that information regarding your participation in technical committees or working groups, for example, may be made available to your company’s primary representative and to DAA’s staff members.  
**Administrators and Moderators**

  If you contact a DAA Administrator or Moderator, we collect information that helps us categorize your question or report, respond to it, and, if applicable, investigate any breach of our Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy.  We also may use this information to track potential problems and trends in order to improve our services to you and to the community as a whole.

  **Group Participation**

  We may collect information when you use the site, such as when you join and participate in any group, participate in any polls or surveys, or otherwise interact with other users within the community.

  **Links to Third-Party Sites and Services**

  The site may provide links to third-party sites for the convenience of our users. If you access those links, you will leave our site. DAA does not control these third-party sites and cannot represent that their policies and practices will be consistent with this Privacy Policy. For example, other sites may collect or use personal information about you in a manner different from that described in this document. You should be aware that materials available through third-party sites may be protected from unauthorized copying and dissemination by U.S. copyright law, trademark law, international conventions, and other intellectual property laws, and the usage of such materials may be subject to limitations that are more or less restrictive than those expressed herein. Therefore, you should use other sites with caution, and you do so at your own risk. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any site before submitting personal information.

  We may receive information when you use your account to log into a third-party site or application in order to recommend tailored content to you and to improve your user experience on our sites.  We may provide reports containing aggregated impression information to third parties to measure Internet traffic and usage patterns.

  **HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

  When you join the DAA, you acknowledge that information you provide on your membership profile may be seen by others and used by DAA as described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. 

  If you are a registered member of DAA, you should be aware that some items of our personal information may be visible to other members and to the public.  DAA’s member database may retain information about your name, e-mail address, company affiliation (if an organizational member), and such other personal address and identifying data as you choose to supply.  That data may be generally visible to other of our members and to the public. Your name, e-mail address, and other information you may supply also may be associated in DAA’s publicly accessible records with our various committees, working groups, and similar activities that you join, in various places, including: (i) the permanently-posted attendance and membership records of those activities; (ii) documents generated by the activity, which may be permanently archived; and, (iii) along with message content, in the permanent archives of DAA’s e-mail lists, which also may be public.   
**Consent to Use by DAA**

  DAA may use personal information to provide services that support the activities of the organization, DAA members, and their collaboration on DAA activities. When accessing the site, your personal user information may be tracked by DAA in order to support collaboration, ensure authorized access, and enable communication between members.

  The personal information you may provide to DAA may reveal or allow others to discern aspects of your life that are not expressly stated in your profile (for example, your picture or your name may reveal your gender). By providing personal information to us when you create or update your account and profile, you are expressly and voluntarily accepting the terms and conditions of our Terms of Use and freely accepting and agreeing to our processing of your personal information in ways set out by this Privacy Policy. Supplying information to us, including any information deemed “sensitive” by applicable law, is entirely voluntary on your part. You may withdraw your consent to DAA’s collection and processing of your information by changing closing your account.

  **Communications from DAA**

  We use the information you provide to customize your experience on the site.  We may communicate with you using email or other means available to us regarding the availability of services, service-related issues, or promotional messages that we believe may be of interest to you.  We may, for example, send you welcome messages, emails regarding new features or services, and promotional information from DAA, or our affiliates, members, and partners.  You may opt out of receiving promotional messages from DAA by following the instructions contained in the email.  As long as you’re a registered user, however, you can’t opt out of receiving service messages from us.  DAA may also use personal information in order to customize content on the site to you, such as news relevant to you or to your industry or company. 

  **Communications from Others**

  Member contact information may be provided to other members on a secure site to encourage and facilitate collaboration, research, and the free exchange of information among our members.  Please remember that any information (including personal information) that you disclose on our site, such as forums, message boards, and news groups, becomes public information that others may collect, circulate, and use.  Because we cannot and do not control the acts of others, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose information about yourself or others in public forums such as these.

  **Sharing Information with Members and Affiliates**

  DAA may share your personal information with our members and affiliates, as necessary to provide you with the services on the site.  From time to time, member information may be shared with event organizers and/or other organizations that provide additional benefits to our members.  By providing us with your personal information during the user registration process and by agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our storing, processing, and distributing your information for these purposes.

  **Sharing Information with Third Parties**

  Information you put on your profile and any content you post on the site will be seen by others.  In keeping with our open process, DAA may maintain publicly accessible archives for our activities.  For example, posting an email to any of DAA’s hosted mail lists or discussion forums, subscribing to one of our newsletters or registering for one of our public meetings, may result in your email address becoming part of the publicly accessible archives. 

  Content contained on the site may result in display of some of your personal information outside of DAA.  For example, when you post content to a forum that is open for public discussion, your content, including your name as the contributor and your email address, may be displayed in search engine results.  In addition, your public profile may be indexed and displayed through public search engines when someone searches for your name.

  You are responsible for any information you post on the site, and this content may be accessible to others.  Accordingly, you should be aware that any information you choose to disclose on the site can be read, collected, and used by other users in the forum, and in the case of forums open to the public, by third parties. DAA is not responsible for the information you choose to submit on the site. 

  DAA does not rent or sell or otherwise distribute personal information that you have shared with us, except as permitted in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. We will not disclose personal information that is associated with your profile unless DAA has a good faith belief that disclosure is permitted by law or is reasonably necessary to: (1) comply with a legal requirement or process, including, but not limited to, civil and criminal subpoenas, court orders or other compulsory disclosures; (2) investigate and enforce this Privacy Policy or our Terms Use; (3) respond to claims of a violation of the rights of third parties; (4) respond to member service inquiries; (5) protect the rights, property, or safety of DAA, our users, or the public; or (6) as part of the sale of the assets of DAA or as a change in control of the organization or one of its affiliates or in preparation for any of these events.  DAA reserves the right to supply any such information to any organization into which DAA may merge in the future or to which it may make any transfer in order to enable a third party to continue part or all of the organization’s mission.  Any third party to which Foundation transfers or sells its assets will have the right to use the personal and other information that you provide in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. 

  **Polls and Surveys**

  DAA may conduct polls and surveys of our users, and your participation in this type of research is at your sole discretion.  DAA may follow up with you regarding your participation in this research.  You may at any time opt out of participating in our polls and surveys.

  **Data Protection**

  Given the international scope of DAA’s activities, personal information may be visible to persons outside your country of residence, including to persons in countries that your own country’s privacy laws and regulations deem deficient in ensuring an adequate level of protection for such information.  If you are unsure whether this Privacy Policy is in conflict with applicable local rules, you should not submit your information. If you are located within the European Union, you should note that your information will be transferred to the United States, which is deemed by the European Union to have inadequate data protection.  Nevertheless, in accordance with local laws implementing the European Union Privacy Directive on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, individuals located in countries outside of the United States of America who submit personal information do thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this Privacy Policy and to its transfer to and/or storage in the United States of America. By utilizing the site and/or directly providing personal information to us, you hereby agree to and acknowledge your understanding of the terms of this Privacy Policy, and consent to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States and/or in other jurisdictions as determined by DAA, notwithstanding your country of origin, or country, state and/or province of residence.   
**YOUR OPTIONS AND OBLIGATIONS**  
**Rights to access, correct, or delete your information; closing your account.**  
You may access, modify, correct, or delete your personal information controlled by DAA regarding your profile or close your account. You can also contact us for any account information which is not on your profile or readily accessible to you.  If you close your account, all of your content will remain visible on the site.

  You should be aware that information that you’ve shared with others or that others have copied may also remain visible after you have closed your account or deleted the information from your own profile. In addition, you may not be able to access, correct, or eliminate any information about you that other users have copied or exported out of the Sites, because this information may not be in our organization’s control. Your public profile may be displayed in search engine results until the search engine refreshes its cache.

  **Data Retention**

  We will keep your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to comply with our legal obligations, even after you’ve closed your account, such as to meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes between users, to prevent fraud and abuse, or to enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.  We may be required to retain personal information for a limited period of time if requested by law enforcement.  We also may retain indefinitely non-personally identifiable, aggregate data to facilitate our ongoing operations.  

  **Your Obligations**

  Be respectful and courteous.  The DAA is a community group, and you have certain obligations both to the DAA and to your fellow users. 

  In order to ensure the integrity of the DAA community effort, you must respect the terms of our Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use, any other applicable policies of the DAA, as well as the rights of other community users, including their intellectual property rights. 

  You must not upload or otherwise disseminate any information that may infringe on the rights of others or that may be deemed to be defamatory, injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic, or that may otherwise violate the purpose and community spirit of the DAA or its members.

  If you violate any of these guidelines or those detailed in our Terms of Use, the DAA may, at its sole discretion, suspend, restrict, or terminate, your account and your ability to access the site.

  **Opting Out**

  From time to time DAA may email you electronic newsletters, announcements, surveys or other information. If you prefer not to receive any or all of these communications, you may opt out by following the directions provided within the electronic newsletters and announcements.

  **Contacting Us**

Questions about this Privacy Policy can be directed to info@digitalanalyticsassociation.org.
